Like.
To go.
To pay.
To keep.
Our.
Eye.
That's my job right. Where you. Can shop
town where you can meet
your. Charge cash. Card
a good pair Robert holiday the
game's long straight hour rain or
it's not apparent on
ground zero if you take
a look at this Battlestar I think it's
serious enough to report I don't know just
like something or
a put my. Boys going to have to carry me
I'm going to apply for the infantry fire
plan was made to
a temperamental mayor that's the first good
New Year almost never heard Go on good
or get it for average.
Family one so hard headed you wouldn't
touch him I told you before we started you
had that kind of chain on too tight.
That's the first time saddest ever tried
putting
a curb on your tongue. Nobody
else ever tried it. Those
attacks when you started as to handle
a horse or how to place we know how to
harness you know how to harness Negroes down
says. The strap across the back.
When are you going to take
a punch you. Took us to graduation. I waited
four years I guess I might not always
. The IT.
Breaking out of the American you
is it now exists the basis of my.
And that destruction must be made upon
the issue of negro slavery and not know
whether. The union must then be reorganized
on the great principle of emancipation
. This subject is vast in its compass.
Terrifying in its prospects but
sublime and beautiful in its. Life devoted
to it would be no police or second.
If the federal government and its Constitution
are opposed to my way of thinking.
The fault is not mine that there is and I
shall continue to oppose them with every
means and every weapon at my disposal
wrote that inflammatory by. A wise man
by the name of John Brown Why do you get
that's my business if you don't like it
either that listen you made
it for me didn't take it in
a way like fury metaphor you tried evolutionist
of I'm evil but I came from Kansas
every minor Comanche an attorney and no
regulation again to getting his own ideas
but there is one against Reading treasonable
policies you'll find the truth had to
take. This right or I know the truth
of this problem far better than you do
the south of settlers
and it's down time in
a certain way but not through the propaganda
of renegades like this John Brown or
any of his followers You mean that renegade
line to include may look up your arse
of Allegiance and answer that for yourself
I answer that right here and. I've taken
a lot from use. For fifty years now you've
been watching your precious family trees
with the sweat of negro slaves piling up
wealth and snobbery until now you think
you own the government and the army
and anybody who disagrees with you is
a lying renegade rabble rousing traitor
you get this from the steward.
You know you other Mason Dixon plutocrat.
Time is coming and the rest of us are
going to like you when you are
kind of the face of the year.
When you're when
you're.
On
your
. Own
you're.
On your own time I've been
aware that
a disturbing force has been active among
the right to make it the exact nature of
this subversive campaign and the persons
responsible but it has not been fully
known to us until this month joint I have
rerolled of the academy you should be
discharged from the service and your
associates are no less guilty for that part in
this outrageous affair and really any blame
in this matter some time to find me my
sole responsibility that's not quite
true sir it was my fault we're all equal
responsible that's right but if I believe
that you would get the loans to it I
should have sent for you alone as for you
Custer and the rest of you you must be
taught that lying to protect
a friend is sometimes an extremely dangerous
practice I'm not so greatly concerned
about the fight itself as I am about its
cause all seven of human violated the
first being the military conduct the
traffic and violent exchange of political
ideas which are not the affairs of an
American soldier you must be punished and
punished severely I should request of the
waterpot went upon your graduation next
week that all of you will be assigned to
the most dangerous branch of the United
States Army. Second United States government
stationed at Fort Leavenworth in the
Kansas City.
That's all good dismissed.
Sanford cadet greater. How can you talk
a little more one time than they say
a lot of people laugh that cat
reacted you so much while we cannot.
Be cannot drive again the trash talking
about I go about that at last I would like
get you boys out there man I miss
my step on the ground already.
And butts were found in Iraq but it
doesn't. Get a letter written by
a member of the abolitionist body strapping
him to distribute them among those
cadets to appear to be sympathetic
to their cause. And only send
a couple activity of us been
going on long enough and
a clever idea of the appellate conspirators
to plant an agent. Or dishonorable
discharge will be drawn up
a glance and you'll be given until sundown
to remove yourself and your personal
belongings from the limits of West Point.
You can tell Mr Still attorney that he'd
be smart to stay in the Army right in the
middle of
a trial now. Get it when you have to
buy. It modern medicine Oh I.
Get it I'm
a model you so. Good at
Georgia customs Oh. Thank
you said James Longstreet South Carolina
thank you for and that's going to
charity do you know. That
it Jane be good thank you
thank you for. That and
John look Kentucky thank
you got it Robert on
a cancer territory. And
it just looks genius. And it's
giong it's perfect that if
you stick it. To your boss would make
a lady out of you not just talk
back. Question to you Oh I.
Get that Robert Davis. Thank you
it is now my great honor and
privilege to introduce the Secretary of
War of the United States of America the
honorable Jefferson Davis thank offering
to send gentlemen to the class of eighteen
fifty four are now welcome guests and
their very proud family as I don't keep you
separate and very long as I am ourself
once sat in your brightest and endured in
a terminal board dressed by our very own
rank Cashin Jim. When I was a secretary
a war on this nation I have
a serious obligation towards each new
officer of the Army before any enters into
active search. And that obligation is to
make clear and definite his responsibility
to his government we are
a new nation among the powers of the world
just eighty years ago we were fighting
desperately for our freedom and we're still
fighting to keep it we are not sharing
a wealthy nation except in spirit and that
unity of spirit is our greatest strength
you know man have but one duty one don't
know America. Well you're wrong for having
a loyalty and the grace of God that our
nation should have no fears for the future
and your own lives we're not going to spend
in the noblest of all cultures so it
depends on the rights of men were all.
Literal Oh my god
the further
her are revolving.
Ergo. Job.
Up the for. Loving
Father.
Of
a. Dollar.
You
from.
The rural poor in the US again.
And again. That I think is the eleven word
it did change this together it doesn't
go any further but her I don't think going
to happen is not there yet someday I'll
get a real railroad to
open it up there to set up
a renovate. Or not are you know Sharknado
need to learn. That they can't tell
a boy to build up for the last time I had
to get out and help jab would be answered
by the first time you wrote me
I had to change your diapers.
Learn on my belly looks like you're going
to Hades I guess one. That's been telling
us about that rare accent of
a cell on the most of the day spreads to
the US namely the stuff to get down the
railroad over blood so brown like cancer
patients others would use it we're losing
thousands of pioneer to the are going for
you they start right around us we heard
about the raid are somewhat of
a Leslie what is the true situation out
here so. Kansas is a territory not
a state we're ready to join the union but
the big question is whether we're going
to slave state or free state one side is
most of Kansas pro-slavery people came
from the south the other side of the
abolitionists made by John Brown the sons I
mean those two elements they make as
a boiling pot of rebellion and massacres
that's why the Army sent two boys are
beautiful Another way to say so citation
by the middle of the biggest with
essentially. You know the first time I saw
you at the graduation I thought of what
the boy said when he first met Joseph that
he said I never knew this savage land
they call America pretends perfect beauty
and more for. Thank you for laughing
Yes And then George been
using it for years have
a job which I think is I think I get to
say. You would like him thinking now you
are going to tell me something more about
Kansas guess what he did on Saturday
night funny. Well is that I
remember accidentally takes
a bath never have gets down is that the
only two that have this you can expect to
get. By the way they have
a common name because gosh how do we on
this because in my backpack it's fact they
were so sure I was going to be applied.
But any part of the price he. Said like
that around me to me to make you. A
conductor and what are you going to do
about that what. I'll end of that. Day
and I don't know them they go
ahead right now let's go X.
Get in the right direction where evidently
and I don't want any trouble you Mr and
you better leave us alone. This
country's coming to. Stop shaking
hands nothing to worry about my half an
hour from the board if we don't hurry their
way across the border All right go ahead.
Are you taking the negroes What business
is that of you or we're asking the
questions they bring about the papers.
That might mean something we did
not tell you. Don't you make
a move. We're taking you on them over this
brainless to the middle of the market
about any.
Possible route but they will do.
Well you know that. There's
a trouble maker of blame trying to sneak
across state lines. I'm going to murder
jihad for that land bank. Point. Out
about one of John Brown's Kirby letter
that I don't know about you get I mean
aren't getting a they know you a spot on
a car but on getting out of the way again
I don't get excited now by the way.
That's what they mean when they call it
Bloody Kansas and there would be any peace
on the side of
a trail while John Brown or any
of his followers are alive. This
is the president said I would come down
here to Wichita in the new year but the
office will read along the
Cymru realize they are
a lot in the Senate and that will be our
first picture perfect little as to which
is right over the trade
Absolutely if I get
a stud to live in back to say they're ready
to put up the money issues we can prove
that
a railroad through can to the states and
replace the oil yet made the cement this
much I clean forgot to make
good. Money Pedro I know
a lot of studying how to run your business
class that tries it true way to show you
want to start worse so that your clothes
will be the grease on your nose all your
friends in Boston think enough. To get it
I don't much care if you're gonna keep
your nose in a paper in
a way I keep my mammy says. Little
done anything getting paid. By If
you tell me. Just tell us why the name
silly when I said goodbye to the dust I'm
glad to make you feel the sun but. I know
you didn't buy the rest of your movie but
I suppose your figure Homer in
a female central belt we don't really
see what you see your brain you think
physically impossible why you ignorant.
You are terribly frightening when you can
hear. Me hear. You gentlemen of
reason by any chance interesting
employment. We lost our watch we didn't
have no idea time I ought to give you both
your time to try you out when kind of
you've been run over you see we had to buy
these nicknacks Well we sort of got
a gal in Santa Fe You really are steadier
and what do you mean we are engaged or.
Have. You set up housekeeping
a sad affair is this just
a feeling really oh or she wants to try
to one of em fancy freaks like and vice.
Pretty quick your answer to vet techs.
Are you I am wrong casting. Are I
have to work out as you go and jump to it.
No matter how I did that thing or start
where and if.
I'm going to put your new officer straight
from the start this is Fort Leavenworth
and not West Point you were sent here to
man up front to your garrison three of the
officers you're supposed to be replaced
things are very back of the hill in the
little military cemetery the other four
haven't been found yet the regiment of
Mounted Rifles has only one job to keep
the peace in Kansas and we're here alone
there's no other forth between our
sunset of faith and we're proud of that
responsibility we've got
a tough reputation in the Army but they
respect us in the West see that it stays
that way. Order of the day but as
long as Friedan on a day thank B.
Troop and put them through close order
drill but then stored in Custer will take
eight man as an escort for the right
caravan leaving at noon for New Mexico or
other usual supplies report
to me for final orders.
If they want to keep all cases of Bibles
near the tailboard they're only going to
short haul for sure we'll
look at it let's go.
Buy ready to wear ready if
you are good I hope you have
a nice flight him one on the other can I
lose money when trying to say that he is
a Quaker with black Just keep your eyes
open boys move fast you like the scenery
but don't trust. Them I said
good bye good bye guys that.
Was. The fucking total mandatory for
a. Film of all the fat that they.
Had. Tied up in time I guess
that way I'll get to work at.
A stoplight and. Write the or.
I got a lot I wait
a minute I come from one man who has
tough not asked to help us. Out when
flooded the top one hundred five job
there is nothing left the name of the
well are you doing here thing that made
that way to me the other way around only
convert to the idea that the things that
man John Brown behind every bush. Not that
I mind how much it's being with me over
six weeks just on my getting started Time
to play and I got
a few minutes left so I've got to be
fast you haven't exactly flow for
a couple of days never dated
a pair with you in Georgia charged borrowed
you are one of them might about it look
in my mind as one kind of
a biker I'm completely crazy about. Now
let me finish I think morning about the
say that it never be I mean probably be
a widow in two weeks Hi Steve have you
thought of any particular names of the
children nobody serious right now this might
be the most precious moment I lived I
hope not now the least Haven't you got any
article. Is ahead because they rightly.
I don't know
a thing about you to not rather think you're
wonderful. But then he has dug out his
headmen which is
a. Mess but at least you let me
kiss goodbye I want to. Know well
it's quite another no thanks I don't
live where I have no say this is
quite
a surprise the couple's looking at you says
it's very rich my best equipped at this
outlet right well enough that George don't
belong in this list again we're due to
leave in
a minute now to something I've got to tell
you I'm head over heels in love with.
You sound just like an echo
kid but man runs drugs
a man can't buy something
else that's why I got
a real competition how do you
think that a girl that asked
a question I thought to tell me the
truth and then both the crazy Get gone
a little girl lacquers through yesterday
from just your throat still sounding
choking your head about the
buzz saw water when you're
a first and all you'll get
to leave is our magic have
a love with the sun make up
will be. Hard but. When my
not even
a little Joe get our. Money even if we
don't get painted the right don't God with
Pray Love All right thank you say the harvest
that up that way home. Lane five per
se just a hour long enough
and the fact a reality sorry
a. Bar I am a lot. Of
a God I said Can I have
a word to Qantas ever so I said
I'll worry about that but I have
a reality
a the I love all of
a lovely thank you. I'll run the race
they are like
a little baby it's you know I want those
two boys I'll give you three to one I can
name the winners. That's
ridiculous. For anyone.
That's ever been good for. Me.
And or not don't volunteer is not the
wunderkind isn't equipped to display their
weapons to public view but that they
understood the go ahead. One I'm also happy to
pass by on them although that our plans
will be known to ourselves alone. That they
join me in the clear knowledge that all
traders of the code must die. Wherever
caught and proven to be guilty. Tell
them that we stand by one another while
a drop of blood from me but under no threats
or pressure do we make an impression.
I get back to. My bank and that's fine I
don't turn back I don't care about way
to kind but I'm trying to see that
they've all of us out of Lebanon.
It's been too late with the
trouble right now so we had
a date telling it had water I think these
and then I can tell my family get. The
credentials from Illinois you've got
a long way to go the rest of us we came
here to fight slavers the sooner the better
that's good we'll put you to work at once.
Because when I look after the gentleman
on the slate putting over the work. We've
received the news we've been waiting for
a break and greater.
Effect than any sense out.
Of it. That are at first either.
But it happened. For the
negro you were told to bring
a couple of pro-slavery strata gravitas
on the train ahead one of them jumped the
you left for help us to go alone or save
yourself to do it father trust me or them
directly through. You
here by my instructions.
Really wants.
All of you don't know when your name. Was
once you sent the raisins to stabilise
your own Ah you have delivered into my hands
the precious me of continuing Di Ollie
we're. The Lord our God is
a great God Almighty in
a terrible regard if not persons nor taken
growing. The Lord on my own I wore.
My right hand to become glorious through.
By right handle God killed the enemy.
Or run over you what that I was not in but
a text they got pretty bad but again I
can also look across the river and then
without
a day of time you know that I'm glad we're
leaving civilization it's too dangerous
for people of
a man to run into some of them abolitionists
want but most of us are John Brown
a coward so much that
all the cars I know is
a dirty old when back. Thank you get your
time. You know your lead in Elvis told
him how to kill it off the lot and I were
friends of mine and they jammed all down
well for them again as there is not
sure like to meet up with a chemist
a John Brown got no quarrel with people
like you attack me too much better to leave
him alone and get married now even if
they are no friends of mine I showed
a commitment to tie.
Rod. With them and the lack of friends
far we have common highwaymen. We
have
a right to cause that's the way to live an
honest like I don't want to recognize it
all over the long God
will do it I come to.
Know and I agree but believe me know.
How to say good morning happy holiday
weekend that's right that's my name is Miss
Jonathan Smith of Newton look and we do
for you I believe you are carrying some
freight consigned to me might be if you got
some to show for it I have this receipt
from the shipper. Come along way with an
empty wagon empty Mr Smith and it's about
a hundred miles from here my home is in
Newton's it but my place of business is
much closer to the true Oh I say I thought
you know it does look pretty fresh and
cases of Bibles as right and wrong when
one fact is liable for the parson Jason
Brandywine in.
The dug out of the Bible that's why
the far. That's funny thing I've seen
a fellow somewhere where it
seems to me then the kind of
a face should forget Mary now. Wait
a minute I know and some magazine
the Atlantic I think for
a lady there from Boston or is
a missionary. That's coming out. But
a lot of bad credit over across the river
late unless there's that murder and got
John Brown's on the loose again but
a kid dear I feel fine thank you we show.
This tough story of having battled.
I want to know you want to read
you saw one and it says yes.
So it's.
Just
a minute. And I can see
the Bible. There you are
going to put your hands up and came on up.
And I'm here tonight no more joint you're
going to. Bring up Bill I can but I
quickly will go to page. All right get
a move on there one of the ones marked
by. A chapter but. Our friend writer.
Well this is a soap opera. That commission
a cavalry to last. I see you've got
a commission you're after you know these
men are writers yes they're very well this
one Stuart comes from a rich slave
owning family in Virginia he called you
a lying renegade lunch and I jumped in
to. Turn brown him john brown on brown I
have nothing personal against human but I
will deal harshly when any interference.
So. I might have known you'd wind up with
this outfit that's one of the challenges
of the Emmys to it they don't teach you to
think ahead that they once my thing they
can add back on an enemy without first
making sure he's. The All the best.
In the satellite so that killing just to
satisfy your personal. One moment or one
mock you any day but no
nominee I intend to be
a marksman. Back to you or greater. Back
here or did all of you I've given you care
warning you can keep goods or
lose them if you wish. Move on.
I don't want another case of charged
contraband rifles and ammunition gosh and
we've been delivering Bibles with triggers
on the tank attacks everybody thank God
opened fire and that.
Morale in the Senate will
not hurt any mom and.
Dad. To get in the way. Of
the not like I have to wait
a minute they are number three to one of
the banks and other stock out of come up.
Paddling down the bombing M M M.
M M Thanks pal if I get your metal box.
Full of lying on the small.
The show.
Were all.
I couldn't help but I couldn't do anything
because nobody's going to hurt you right
Jason Brown Rat You want to come around and
share I never did anything you made me
go
a lot I never killed anyone I swear I'm
getting out I'm quitting. It's got to
take me with you all right bring
a hot tub George I got started to carry
him back. Boys there they heard.
This father's madness really
striking out. If there's
a purpose behind and madness one that
can easily be dismissed. Don't you see
in the middle on a compass have to. Have
a whole car to swing around in but always
welcome back I'm not driving and. Yes
This boy is now annoys him and his life
never affected our friends him and never
will but it is not job decide who's right
and who's wrong about slavery any more on
this is John Brown. I guess
you're right yeah I'm sorry.
For the things we got in there but it means
and next time we're going to college
and let me do the future for
my goes inside of our own.
Then up. You'll bust
a little it's like unless your legs are
standing that your thank you one hundred
years old or more. Or where
the firearms are contraband
against you think we do except it goes
back to this phrase if we don't what the
accurate contains I'm just asking that's
all doesn't it seem strange to you the Dr
J.
Boyce Russell the most prominent religious
leader in America should be sending right
most doctors Bibles to John Brown How can
I control the Marquis of rates we want to
see three tons of gunpowder marked pretty
well then you'll have to examine every
creature all eyes are all we know this
contraband may have been slipping through
for months chase but sometimes. You've got
nothing to be afraid of you'll be honest
but. I want to go on my list includes.
To Bother the mention the ship and the
Broncos when he discussed his
plant at me. Ever confided. To.
Fred not of the. Where the
headquarters where they were. A
half
a dozen places. You
. Know why about it.
Guns are no mistake any one of the best
interest of Kansas are can tell you that
when you look at push buttons ordered off
I got about the holidays we got as much
interest in Kansas the United States
government and I don't type or invest we were
here before the army came in by gun free
we'd be able to have our if you think you
can. Post Georgia when you
find. The too badly to
frighten well even media
they haven't sound assembly.
Or that you call me at gol darned bandy
legged push back I'll go on he says he got
it right. But. Doesn't tell people to
kill one another does he mean this.
Is a. Good man or a. Chain saw
a lot of. People take care of.
They get down on their knees and
beg them for the. Piece of the
sword. And then Raider Kitzmiller.
I was there. They saw Dad and tried
to stop them but they must be
a sack. That's all that. We're starting
at once I'll take the first true
West to come see the art you want Custer
would take the first but don't have the
truth and searched thoroughly from Clinton
to Dutch Henry's crossing is that there
are these are your orders find John Brown
and bring him back here alive if possible
his forces well are now in stronger numbers
we also suspect that new volunteers
a distinction from these to join him be
on the lookout for them as well it's hard
to respect the folks back in the day.
But for us the more No one can.
You committed no crime you
can pray to God I'm sick of being afraid
I'm sick of hiding like a hundred things
a lot I was very like other people you.
Know I'm Not that as long as he keeps
killing thinking that he's
right. He can't be right can in.
His reasons they be right. They may
even be great good. But much of the.
Care. And his. Is none.
And I'll never be free of him.
To one of us did. By life
don't mean anything. But if he dies. Then
this whole scheme of his will die with
the better have
a way. Of life. Even if for
years my father against many
South. I'm going to tell you where to find
enough time I'm going to tell you anyway
the house of you will mortgage Palmyra
that's what they want at the headquarters
tell the soldiers. It's been
a fair way. Because life. Gets went south.
And we follow the
old. Bear. How is. That the Dr
one of them can't you tell me at home I
tend to senior even placement father is not
he said he wanted me to tell
soldiers where Palmyra cause
a man into the modern noble
more than. One of us can't.
I'm frightened. That
boy's crippled life. In
a man on the train he died for print and
a man killed him for. One of them is
wrong but which one. Dancer that kept
everybody in America stranded
side yes by Britney by guns in
a way that one day the words will turn
into. A check can't be stopped now have
a sleepy fleet first and then it will be
stuff we hang John Brown and the sock and
set around problem without loss of pride
of being forced into it by bunch of CARE
what is Pi got to do with human lives.
To think kind of come together that.
Come from
a part of it not. I hope
that's going to affect. All
that's May all over come take us or park
and i get us to where I hope you're like
you know that's much the same you were
before us and that's where I learned
a good one more of my account yes I'd like
to at the end just accumulate. A good
bye good bye to. You that.
Don't belong to him
don't. Remember that when I love
him with that name upon the
people that come down and about.
My love pent up eyes I know we didn't do
that I said I could fall in love I got
left and I know we're going to John Brown
with you watch we are we come and join up
who do we face
a couple of flatfooted run fucks like you
in the Army why you gotta Las why you
gotta go I'm
a Slave up the law I have the
right and the right. Path
. He can.
Take it fine tell. Him.
We're trying to find.
Old.
Once when you were about this high tech
swindle brought home a wolf coke with
a broken back. Just
a few weeks but it find it died with his
head in your lap. You prat for days just
was so abruptly brought up to be
a killer like it's far. All of.
The inside pocket gotta do it right now
our economy around pockmarked maybe I had
a drink since no.
Moore.
War rather Moore
Moore. High gets
a pledge. Surely
conventional for Mr Morgan just not the
way we got him the homeowner stuck him in
the bar yes for us looks like the best
kept on we had to get. One hundred hours
worked up about the new man but I can
promise looks like another job or as I read
about it. But he bought it you gave it to
Warner will think yeah they're going to
like Donna and I signed up because you
promised to pay us kind of rattled gang of
us to
a silent fast moving you to fight taught
him how to use easy to write follow orders
to get counted on a sec. I have received
a red cent in three months now what
about it Mr Rader I enlisted you on the
recommendation of friends in the Who said
you would work for the court you've done
your job well I have no complaint up enough
but our plans are ahead of any personal
greed if you feel otherwise you are free
to get out if you must decide here enough
I want only the oil men are on me.
There's no argument with my
loyalty I prove that that's
a lot of the and every other time
we've rated it you had me as
a military expert at
a set price and I'm only asking what's
right we do me and I say the do or receive
it in time only let me
think and beat. Son is
a prisoner in the hands of our
enemy even though he may have
a rope around his neck and
in this all you never fired
a gun and anger in his life but I stand
here powerless to take All right
away well let your next move.
Bible is said and I have written to her
to. Morrow at daybreak we will stroll
Delaware across.
The pond. Well
the major sort of turned it down too but
here we are ten to Jim what do you mean
trailing us half way across Kansas
when I want you to get lost B.C.
I know ever recall of the sure country just
like home plate but you're sure that's
just as dirty I've got a good mind to get
a couple of mules to strap you
on the back and send you home
a fine lookin fer US soldiers you may have
all we need is some of them answered the
cat and in
a cautious and soldiers just our size gets
Cuba. All right get back to the end of
the column go on before I get that you
know we don't have to obey orders since
we're the army. What
we will hear now I had
a. Little kid hears about this
just get him alive as I got
a skin left.
So did. CHARLIE BROWN. How
many men did he have with.
Around
a hundred maybe more.
Than three four hours. We
lost count of time. You know the man that
had the run in with one of the browns on
the train. Bench that yes we're
Free Staters here Brown always knew
we'd get him some day we didn't get our
spurs. Think this man have to bury
a dead. Bessie back to let might we don't
want to make out this is our fight we
don't want your nobody else to finish
it. I'm going to take care of Dan Brown
myself get on your way so you know we got
work to do I know how you man must feel
about this my orders are to break up all
armed forces yours John Brown's or anyone
else I'm sorry but if you organize
under arms I won't be able to draw
a line between us that
suits us it's got to be.
Where you find out if we lose at all the
cavalry from Fort Leavenworth are headed
this way. She will move in can run up
all human get the wagons ready to roll
just food and ammunition with traveling
like moving fast What about any role we can
take all of them we're not taking any.
All old
already.
My children the art of deliverance I
promised you would come. I'm leaving Kansas
now to continue God Oh they were.
So giddy and took ten minutes or.
Did as God said and. It was so that he
did it by night when the minute that we
could city arose early in the morning
behold the altar of Dale was cast off place
Kevin Brown what did it mean what you
going do with US me that you are free the
first of many millions to whom I should
give freedom from sleep as does just fan so
make us free I will go live get food and
shelter there are many good people in
Kansas who will give you work and protection.
From now on you must spend yourselves
and other free men do. My work here
is to reign and will only be blessed
by God with. The cabinet have his
word was free when I when I.
Was all Allah. Allah
God all Allah you know John Brown is
a hundred men we'd better send
a runner back bring at the rest of the trip
but that's not you. I'm going to power
my touch you know about the great need you
had that counts for the change of August
that your chance I'd have to take
a chance on that I'm going to get some
other class take up and I'm going to test
Scotty. I'm trying to send him
back but. Good luck. Said you to
find I still want to turn out a I've got
a job that they think is pretty dangerous
but I think about a spy but he's
a really we're going to have a real cabin
a uniform. Well we might have to be
bad enough but it sure sounds like.
The last god. Way came. Round because.
The whole thing's going to be settled right
here. We came here to fight anyway I am
fine and. You're getting
a good lookin over there here man down
here I feel just like I was taken aback at
the best talk without no sides
only don't know kind of
a to be able to say how could
I talk to in this kind of
a town without arousing suspicion Tom
Foreman right any time a barber to talk to
a stranger he'd love to go crazy. Said.
Pretty good looking horse well as part
of the world. And it's all right for man
dogs but it's pretty hard on women
and horses. Say Look at that bright.
That anomaly or. Maybe just
bought it from somebody
I don't tell. Nobody runs that brand but
a soldier. You keep your
eye on your blanket but.
Still get the creepy feeling about this
but I don't know where this that or that
your triggers. Branches
you that goes away.
That is all. I got announced
we were on the same site
a couple of months ago and I thought. You
probably got me mixed up with somebody
else now Sherry and about to
get a face although I was
a little drunk at the time for us to
play our values they had to fight. Just
a couple of weeks to say no time bothers
a fellow lay trying to fight of
a damn razor rather than tell me to
spend the money yes I heard you got
a pretty tough customers here today I'm
afraid to shave you don't cut my throat I
said You ever run across this famous watch
his name John Brown sure he came in
a once phrase look a man with
a gun is. No bother so. A little red
line that runs all the way around here
anybody below that mark is bound to be home
that's. Say I've got what have I. Now.
Maybe. Well.
Keep your head away.
This is quite an idea still.
Coming in alone look around.
As it's one of the race I know what I don't
applaud I swear that I don't know from
Adam. If you figure that my next move is
plain enough and I just had
a hand of spies and we caught him red handed
same treatment for and again when you
get this make you quite
a hero still at the class of fifty four
return on the body for your funeral and
then hang your picture in the West Point
library its worst place to. Get him out of
here it wasting time just telling
a last few words with an old classmate
of. And I had them coming to me.
Telling you that. We're going to give you
a good looking but. We
care what it takes Chester he was sent
here to spy My advice to get rid of that
screen and write. What did you hope to
achieve by coming alone Elmire the Army has
orders from Washington to bring you to
trial I hope I came face to face with you
first
a lot of unnecessary bloodshed might be
avoided the old man and my we were innocent
enough to think that I would
surrender my soul to you without
a fight I hope that you might consider
yourself and not do that at the people in
America believe in your say
a lot of them even condone your
methods that will guarantee you
a public trial I'm not on trial
but the nation itself are you too
stupid and blinded by
a uniform to see what I see that dark and
evil curse laying all over this land
carnal sin against God can only be wiped
out in blood why in blood the people of
the Jena consider the resolution
to abolish slavery for
a long time they sense that the tomorrow
and the rest of the South will follow the
Chinese example well last
time time time. For thirty
years I waited for the South to claims
its soul of this crime since childhood I
have been possessed of the fire of correcting
this wrong I tried peaceful agitation
. God is my witness I tried
peaceful means failed long ago
now I shall force
a decision by bringing both sides in the
armed conflict letters words talk time is
ended for that strength an
action I wanted now not
a boy crying in the wilderness but
a David armed with the power
and the glory. Say that had
a son and son that was there
to disbarment over the enemy.
What are you trying to tell
me. And Absalom died that.
Day. So be it. My son has
paid for the sins of this
world with his life as once did the
Son of God. It shall not be in vain.
But if you kill me on a family will crash
will in the end. I advised you to find
a nice video maker.
Like barbers know how. To love to live in
a real legal outcome to it from where you
go but I don't know why it wasn't taken
out that way or took the same fellow that
a brown. Kid is greater.
Than you will dare when we get back I was
troubled on your liver and Farmer kill
your carcass I guess I worry
a. For
me.
My culture altogether is with the here my
words. An enemy to the cause is entered
are made out to lead by night for the purpose
of planning our destruction. That and
that is never fail to come once again to
our protection not with malice or events
that we take this man's life but in just
retribution big fits all enemies of
mankind. All enemies of God. That.
Talk like.
First. Off I don't go on pricing.
All right just have. A lot
of them just don't go
way.
Out that's too tight many don't tell me how
to do this bowling I mean rabbits want
books all my life when they was Babies R
M one and two when they grow double talk
on too much calling and then I
ramped up and. Out of my to
a house where old John Brown said he's gone
give us freedom but shuck and efficient
cancer this freedom then I got no useful
it will serve Me neither I just want to
get back home to Texas and
said Kill Kingdom go.
For
a. While
we had
a nice right old way. Yet you are to get
away and I do not think I had one tramp
your already dollars heard him utter You
joke at that with me you shut my adult
well as one might imagine. From now on
if I never meant and against. That I got
a record for such
a project that even death Iraq
touch is finished. Last broken
forever.
By the guy several were for
do I not find favor with. Why
has to leave the weight
of all these people upon.
This fine which I waited all over to
fix your comment the burning bush.
Let tax be no peace at all is fine until
we aren't going to start till the night in
a. Nice Once you spot the Philistines
by now the fury on Iraq upon these
blind misbegotten for. I shall
be dire I can't I son Brown
still be the support of
your home. Alone I love.
The look gentleman with the beginning
of the railroad instead of
a Israel God stretched my way right across
the old prayer right over gather down
into the territory of the next Sunday we
can tell our grandchildren that we open
the doors of America to the Great Southwest
one way to get us into railroad I'm not
doubting any. At the end of John Brown
without beginning to be will cost
a lot more blood and grief but it's going
to be where that. Timing the bill on the
to change is and blow the whistle that
will. A day you can live for and following
the.
Rules
of poor old girl the old old
age old the old in the early old
the old and
a little girl named old
Ole all over
a little old oh
a whole. Ole
USA in the hole they all over her little
ole Oh OK It's
a gold. Thank you.
Regulation boy Thanks that's the day I
think they're just going to sell the place
because I'm not on the Santa Fe Well these
young men have all been promoted were
ordered back to Washington and then new
like it ever was I had to wait ten years on
my captaincy and I also thought
this by voting to my wife
a night that's what would you like
some advice yes I've heard that idea.
Well I think around out the state or
socialist wanting to let go it may be that
fine.
But you have to go apply for tell them
a few with the best
barbecue along the scent of
a trail I just made for this sort of casual
How do I know he's going to take us up
on it when you start fitness but you'll
think about it take it up an out and then
you still be hard to untangle
Well I don't. Oh I still got
a hunch we should have and first. We
took the horns off of the Denali.
But I think at the age of
thirty dollars a body boy
a month. And I think it. Thought it was
well you know this and that what he wanted
to do with your act OK. Back
to the same thing as you I.
Want to draw straws for this time let
me do it what are we going to have
a thing like that I don't try to
set enjoy the moonlight. All right
a task to get. Him
to do the lines that
are the target left. I
asked George's got telegraphed can't you
have the floor George Well I don't know
just how to start at that there's an old
Indian woman who hangs around the fourth
Kelsey but sports she's supposed to be
a wonder at it as well. Yesterday Well
she said I'm going to get married soon
to
a very beautiful girl such as you're.
Pretty slick opening remarks. Kids
were you ever by any chance
a blind plan no not even if they are you
sure this old woman's never been wrong
before absolutely sure well
maybe she still right there's
a whole lot of beautiful blondes in
the world George let's ask let's wait
a minute. Are you in love with
him and not with me. I guess I
you couldn't marry him wait
a minute I can handle this protest from
passion you really mean if you hadn't asked
me anything. All right I said their own
thing and men could have been most perfect
. Now is that it is.
You. Want to but you're
going to bring him to come
sometime and that needs.
To come up to because.
I knew. How much steak it you know the
lingo says that this is one of the last
times when all of
a speedy gathers friends. Because it's
an extensible I'm going to be the first
general. When Mr when he got. Them
across America and let them fall
through something. Because. She
says that one day you'll be famous
made great best. But bitter enemies.
Apocrypha I think it hurt kus the Sheraton
long straight man amazed I know she's
crazy but in
a big up is all they can judge until their
forces now it to you is well I'm not
talking I'm honest but asked about going
to fight about that was going to start it
. Whether this one to me that last.
Time or make the gratuity is at least.
Mechanical on guns in terms
of the sister most damage.
I have what's this try to get us down
he says the fight has already started.
Somewhere in the last man
is lying too much. Not
a scary moment. Two of us will
help determine. Can stop in.
Front. Of our farm an
awful lot of I'm one of the.
Areas where I would attack first
the arsenal of Harpers Ferry. Give me only
a hundred good Dr RUSSELL Well I have been
God fearing man who believe in the call
I will lead them through virgin brows the
thousands of discontented slate who will
flock to join. Don Buddhists up through
the Carolinas Georgia Alabama Mississippi
then with the Empire nation in
a state of chaos we can take our own
turn if you consider the eye makeup and.
Surely there will be a
few in full force within
a few hours after the first attack let
them come Dr Russell let them try to stop
I've studied that country for years it's
full of good hiding place is natural for
display large forces
a brave man can defy pursuit indefinitely
Mr Rader will go ahead of. Us with his
knowledge of military mothers and our great
advantage of surprise we can outwit the
army at every turn get them around this
planet and all of us might have been mad as
high treason such
a brazen attack would lead to civil war
I second that is exactly what I want is
a job then to destroy the union by and
sort out that it. Hasn't got to what the.
Fight might as well be not
gentlemen I came here to
Boston a great personal risk there's
a price on my head of ten thousand dollars
so my time is precious you'll give me
much help and encouragement up to now
but all that we have done in Kansas and
elsewhere I will be
a waste and let you see it through
the door you're saying how
much money would do me.
Now because the guns ammunition tanks
a complete store supply place and they
are set by perspiring DAYBREAK Monday
October sixth the West Bank with two force
suddenly was complete surprise and move
rapidly to bridge and. Demand all know
what will be demanded of Yes well it never
happened. Get brighter. In
a good time. Well
what you find because anything wrong
average turn itself on the neutral there's
a bridge to the bottom on Iraq at the
bottom you gotta cut the telegraph line to
Washington what about the government are.
Guided by only two winners. And they
distrust matter the place. Actually
this is precisely what I want
because first take Marcus McCarthy and
prevent an attack by the civilians and move
directly on the arse that's something else
but I want to settle our account back in
can't you promise to pay me less doing that
in my name I'm going to demand that our
private matter. Nations are deliverance
not free days are that's putting the cart
before the horse that I've done
a job here nobody else can do so I was
right to come by the Course itself means
nothing I like holding it here where you
went in and you forgot to wipe me by my
husband while I haven't forgotten anything
to get the money the painting you can
afford not to. Thank. You I haven't waited
thirty years to bargain with
a rogue of mine are. Thousands.
More are. All or are
old poor. The old. Old.
Man like an army life I like to see me was
a part of the decision I was head of the
ship down. When I started out come on and
. The emir be invitations he
didn't want them in the light cart
when I got the limitations job came we
getting on our uniforms No sir not unless
you asked to go right
out on them again with
a thousand feet of canvas if you're worried
about stars so big we don't need no
keep the deep.
Little old old old.
Blue glow. And jump. Right to mine.
As the price of much is going to get me
away ALL friend of mine and I'm surprised
that I remember the rest of my life. You
don't know any girl in the kitchen or not
talk to you don't write but I
do thank you story. Alice.
Look one thanks to George just telling me
of the past in the big time of his life
what I can do just and then I found Thank
you yes I haven't told you that but we
have
a deep understand. That is spiritual but
if I'm going to take it you're the best in
life care that it didn't matter it was
OK and I have my faults but I can be
a space but unlike any man that ever
lived. That way he about. Catholics and
I guess we can all have charm and good lucks
to. That's right I'll go jogging and I
say that I'll take it so hard I mean
if something could happen to the.
God I wish we had kept to it that shot
of the physical made together and the
pleasure thank you yes indeed
a great pleasure I had so much
about you kept me. Alive.
But I mean that well as well
as. Phillida Yes of course.
A lot of the pundits Georgia
comics my old sit in the mud.
On
a knife. Edge thank. You
. For the. Present arms but
there is
a scoop. About
this. Company. Right. Right.
Well air I was right out in the middle of
campus facing five hundred crazy fanatics
heavily armed and me with only fifteen
soldiers have been captured how terrified
but if you do I sized up the situation at
a glance dismount and walk straight toward
I'm not alone. My dear young lady there
comes
a time in every soldier's life when he
must stand or fall off and if you know the
army you'd understand that he will have
to face that last. One hundred. Odd with
nothing really.
When you come to meet my. But I can see the
light. In the Government service Yes I
think you need
a job in the next election Oh that's too
bad say you should be in the Army you know
politics don't bother you
rather go fishing anyway five
a little Charlotte said OK to the idea
father like me Captain George. Oh but of
course I'm at the capital at West Point
going to graduate I didn't yesterday. I'm
fine Currently we've heard good things
about you congratulations The captain just
been telling me how he put down the trouble
in Kansas by himself. From the job
proud I was splendid Wasn't there also
a chap named Stuart chipper Stewart connected
with the campaign doing. Yesterday
he was around. Shall we dance. To. The
floor wall old
old pole. That turn.
Up all night. Bar. Move
the goalposts go away eventually
just once already I don't
want her I want to run that lonely Canyon
Catalona Middleboro why it spread still
feel to take over the detail with the man
from. The new punk but I'm not out of the
other stuff not anybody down for you talking
about old friend of yours now trying
to get me to bring you to.
Lose lose lose. Thrill I almost touched.
What are you doing here I came to find you.
Another two segments to look at I'm no
good. Maybe a right. And maybe
a good sense in attending to
the change of things you have
a hard time doing that Suppose I told you
that I left John Brown three hours ago
with
a well armed forces and they're not very
many miles from that were standing. I'd
say you were out of your mind set to
strike at Harpers Ferry on the Maryland
Virginia and then tonight. With reinforcements
over twelve thousand expected before
daybreak and then to think around the plans
to arouse the slaves first in Virginia
and then throughout the south and over
a thousand. Telegraph wires will be cut
and he'll block the railroad and at
daybreak they rush the US take thousands
of weapons with the idea of arming the
negroes. But the situation gentlemen move
from oh I don't know you may be able to
get there ahead of them but if you do
you've got to move fast tonight it's
fantastic our Secret Service reported John
Brown to be out of the country well I
don't know where years I've been with him
every day and every mile since we left
Kansas then why are you informed on it
does get kind of I was in the service not.
Shia and I made
a mistake I didn't know that then but I
do know. I guess some of the things we
learned at West Point today on inside of
us but they but then we realized Anyway I
couldn't stand by and see
my country torn apart by
a madman like Brown I had to
come here this was something
a lot bigger than myself couldn't have
been the size of the reward to look at the
turning men could I said why I came here
and that's the truth. That I am entitled
in
a reward. I'm even willing to go back there
and rejoining tonight just in case you
get suspicious or change its plan. What
more proof do you want to know that I
believe in because it's too dangerous not
to also get your start Colonel to be
ready to leave in an hour the offices are
all here all in that once and proceed
with all speed to our prosperity.
You have your autocratic spirit
yes. I think John Graham
gets
a little tax cuts take and I am sorry I
can't explain I no time I try to keep the
others kept and I think they
accept that. Fact because the.
No moron article. You say no train is due
until well after daybreak notion that
later I rode within ten miles Washington
next year we're going to so long it takes
federal place just. A few hours
get your mind blocked or
a bridge we need blow they are smart they
break Kitzmiller go to the town with
twenty men to get our cities you know
the ones yes breast human follow me.
All. All.
Got your guns.
Allah. Heavenly girl not going
to hear Dharma tell them my
money our bullets that goes guns and
ammunition near the door ready to hop the
police get em up there then Pennsylvania
will be here within the hour and it has an
Arsenal supporters we could stand up the
whole army but about the president getting
what is them. Meaning of this outrage by
a who broke into our homes and dragged us
here to argue I am John Brown of Kansas.
You are prisoners of the provisional
government of the United States the citizens
of Harper's Ferry attempt any interference
I show you you as I see it. Otherwise
you will be peacefully released
when we depart. We must adhere to
a schedule of the precise minute you leave
here ten o'clock by nightfall we should
be thirty five miles in the region what
about the men from Pennsylvania by Leighton
arriving we cannot wait
would not be taking
a long chance no word of us can look at
the harm it even to the three days and
leave the fifteen hundred men out and see
that there's any reason to hurry us up
sceptical I disagree I'm anxious to get
out of here and time is our most valuable
weapon here and commences but that's been
a fatal mistake to many an
expedition My advice is to wait.
A
SEC. To let our people firing at
us just as well mother we can't
go we can't clean our environment.
By the slightest chance
the understand reality.
What is your name bro or if you know about
your life or know what of your fellow
townsmen you will do if I say. Yes.
Last fall I managed
by airing your knives Oh God
Hi Jon Bon promises that if we
leave the arsenal in his hands he will
harm none of us know friend known her
little how do you.
Measure
a scandal can't you understand we're here
in the right just hold their interest for
Also hours and go to all nations we leave
a listener at Harpers Ferry one hour after
the help to profit by by almost two to
one else Mark
measuring
. Moving in to. Take all the weapons and
ammunition you can carry it was. Well
past noon we can wait no longer the
Pennsylvania.
The. Nation will have to start it killed
thirty three wounded by John Brown's And
they did it all for a better. Term
a second post from Rick Mirer. The road
to upper stories plus unable to get.
Traction God had the Winchester. The
Middle East command rushed through
a REAL of our ago they will be
the first arriving to her right
the National.
Mall. Where you're watching later. Today
not thrilled to know what brought it over
there this is the Washington fight but I
don't and my second attack on it I was not
there ordered help on the wagon. But I just
think we had to wait another half hour
it might be a. F.
. Bomb the
F.B.I.
Girl
rather
. The Al
Al the al the
rat. The al.
Waitress. At no cost to hurry.
It sure that we had to do it
yourself I wanted to take it under
a white flag to John Brown rice.
It's been a party Yes and it's
a refusal waiver had to
it right. After this one.
Then they can roam the planet.
No point.
One hundred and one.
We've met before I think
thanks to Mr Rader we now meet again.
Was analyst from the man you're surrounded
once more through your return strength
in supposing that I can be taken against
my will. But your final answer that is we
prefer to die here. I.
Think just being in the right
a gastric band I think you. Owe. To
Q.
Two Q two Q.
Q Q.
Q.
I'm. You.
Won't.
You. Please. Of.
Half. Past.
Half.
Half are
a. Little
. Over.
Half.
Rather. Than the
rap rap rap.
Rap.
He was born. Had caused
him to. Just continue.
Paying much not just when.
He won the land was gone.
I am only walking his dog for
a day and I sure will. Oh my actions
even the follies leading to this
disaster were degree to happen long ages
before this world again. But I cannot
remember a night so darkest
will hinder the coming day. Or
a storm so furious as to Prof and the
return of warm sunshine in the country.
I need John Brown I'm not quite certain
that the crimes of this guilty land can
never be purged away but with
blood. I know it to my mind.
I forgive them and may God forgive
me but they know not what they do.
Little petty thoughts I
tell him I her all such
a little Human Right now the
all
right and there to have given him
a fair trial to the other and I think
the same by giving and receiving
a ring and by joining hands I find out that
there are men and right united forever
with ties that no man shall break asunder
all the years to stir the Shining Path to
run together from this
they can either return it.
All right.
A little. OFF THE
asked. Earlier.
The
other. And. I.
And. Two.
Thousand.